## **Brodie Force**

5 Cemetery Road, Berwick, PA 18603 (570) 817-3776 Brodie.Force@gmail.com

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Working towards getting a computer science degree and an entry-level python certification. 3+ years of computer technology education in I.T. and programming fields; primarily focused on programming. Seeking a position in a company where I can obtain professional work skills and programming experience.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Volunteer,** Elks Lodge 117 W 2nd St, Berwick, PA 18603

March 2021 - 2022

- Assist the chef in preparing orders.
- Deliver orders to tables.
- Assistant during cleanup after operation hours.

#### Sales Associate, Rite Aid

400 W 2nd St, Berwick, PA 18603

June 2022 - Present

- Run the register
- Assist customers
- Stock and Straighten shelves
- Remove old sale tickets
- Replace price stickers

#### **SKILLS**

Programming knowledge: Python, JavaScript, SQL, PHP, HTML, and CSS.

Computer literate with experience in computer maintenance/repair and Linux/Unix.

Cooperative; good team member.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Columbia-Montour Area Vocational Technical School,

Sweppenheiser Dr, Bloomsburg, PA 17815 — Computer Technology

August 2019 - Present

- National Honors Society Member
- Technical Honors Society Member
- Current GPA: 93.780%

#### **PROJECTS**

## 5<sup>th</sup> Annual STEM Hack-the-Box Competition — Bloomsburg High School

Competed to use a mini-computer to "help the community". Worked with a team to program a security camera with facial recognition/tracking. Programmed the camera to move with faces recognized. Explained how the source code works during the presentation.

Last Edited: 2/9/24

#### **REFERENCES**

#### **Chuck Greco**

Computer Technology Teacher, Columbia-Montour Vocational-Technical School 5050 Sweppenheiser Drive Bloomsburg, PA 18603

Phone: (570)784-8040 Email: cgreco@cmvt.us

#### **Karen Markle**

Secretary, Elk's USA 117 W 2nd Street Berwick, PA 18603-4713 Phone: (570)759-8131

Email: berwicksecretary@yahoo.com

## Jenn Moyer

Manager, RiteAid 400 West Second Street

Berwick, PA

Phone: (570)752-5200 Email: Jenn@riteaid.com